[{"value": {"id": 1827298, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 31 of the Strategic Defence Review - Making Britain Safer: secure at home, strong abroad, published on 2 June 2025, who will chair the Cabinet sub-Committee on Space.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827297, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 31 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, when he expects the Cabinet sub-Committee on Space to be established.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827296, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to recommendation 29 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, who will the new defence uncrewed systems centre be led by.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827295, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to recommendation 29 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, how many new staff will be employed as part of the defence uncrewed systems centre.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827294, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to recommendation 29 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 202 what the total cost was of establishing the new defence uncrewed systems centre.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827293, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to recommendation 34 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, what discussions he has had with stakeholders on the successor to the Dreadnought class submarine since 2 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827292, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to recommendation 29 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, where the new defence uncrewed systems centre will be based.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827291, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 27 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, whether he plans to increase funding for (a) a deep precision strike and (b) integrated air and missile defence during the cu", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827290, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 25 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, what powers the Government will hold in reserve should the UK enter a conflict.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827289, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 25 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, which body will be responsible for external scrutiny of UK warfighting readiness.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827288, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 25 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, whether he has a formal date for the implementation of the Defence Readiness Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827287, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 25 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, when he plans to bring the Defence Readiness Bill before Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827286, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 24 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, whether he plans to have discussions with Cabinet colleagues on the (a) protection and (b) defence of critical national infra", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827285, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 24 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, what steps he is taking to support the Royal Navy in taking a (a) leading and (b) coordinating role in securing undersea (i) ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827284, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 23 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, whether he plans to publish a formal policy document on developing understanding of the armed forces among young people in sc", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827283, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 23 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, whether (a) Minister and (b) officials from his Department have had discussions with representatives from the Department for ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827282, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to clause 23 of the Strategic Defence Review, published on 2 June 2025, whether he will have discussions with the Secretary of State for Education on developing an understanding of the armed forces", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827273, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to review the consistency of Sustainable Farming Incentive application decisions made after the scheme was closed.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827272, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support farmers who incurred costs based on an expectation of acceptance to the Sustainable Farming Incentive scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827271, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of long ambulance transfer times for cardiac emergencies on (a) Suffolk and (b) nationally.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827270, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help tackle regional differences in access to specialist care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827269, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70639", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure equal access to advanced cancer diagnostic tools for patients across all regions of the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827268, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70638", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy NHS investment to combat waiting lists in (a) Suffolk and (b) nationally.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827267, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether funding for NHS waiting lists is proportionate to the average waiting list time in each region.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827266, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of regional differences of NHS waiting lists.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827265, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has met with representatives of the Motorcycle Action Group to discuss the role of motorcycling in national transport policy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827264, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to support the transition of motorcyclists from petrol and diesel vehicles to zero-emission alternative.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827263, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to improve road safety for motorcyclists.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827262, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether motorcycling will be included in the Integrated National Transport Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827247, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking in response to publishers disabling video games that have already been sold.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827281, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70594", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has plans to (a) simplify and (b) expand access to (i) business rates relief and (ii) tax support schemes for small hospitality venues in (A) coastal and (B) rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827280, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70593", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to review the \u00a385,000 VAT registration threshold.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827279, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70592", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of recent increases in the National Living Wage on the financial sustainability of small businesses in (a) hospitality, (b) retail and (c) other sector", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827278, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70591", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will meet with representatives from small hospitality businesses to discuss (a) VAT reform and (b) the introduction of sector-specific reliefs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827277, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70590", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent comparative assessment her Department has made on the levels of VAT charged to (a) small hospitality businesses, (b) supermarkets, (c) national chains and (d) delivery platforms.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827276, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70589", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to review the Flat Rate Scheme rules to enable small hospitality businesses to recover VAT on essential inputs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827275, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70588", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a reduced flat rate percentage for hospitality sector businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827274, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70587", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the Flat Rate VAT Scheme on small independent hospitality businesses' ability to claim VAT on (a) food, (b) energy, (c) supplies and (d) other input", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827246, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions she has had with local authorities in Oxfordshire on traffic filters restrictions.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827245, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her policy is on the sale of allotments.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827244, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the QE2 Conference Centre has made representations to Westminster City Council on the operation of the Westminster Arms pub.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827243, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70555", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, further to the letter to the Hon Member for Thirsk and Malton from the Director General of the Propriety & Constitution Group of 23 June 2025, if he will provide guidance to departments from the Propriety and Et", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827242, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70554", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to the Downing Street press release entitled PM call with President Xi Jinping of China: 23 August 2024, what discussions he had with President Xi Jinping during the telephone call on the proposed Chinese Embassy ", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827250, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make it his policy to redirect funding for orphanage economies to fund family strengthening.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827249, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the sustainable impact of the Global Care Reform Campaign, including\u00a0(a) a long-term strategy up to 2030 and (b) adequate resour", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827248, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what international commitments he plans to make in relation to the Global Care Reform Campaign.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827261, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Local Planning Authorities have an up-to-date local plan.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827260, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the decision to end the commissioning of new neighbourhood planning support services on Neighbourhood Plans tha", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827259, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2025 to Question 60598 on Neighbourhood Plans, what guidance her Department has provided to local planning authorities so that they can continue", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827258, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department has taken to protect localism when neighbourhood plans are being created.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827257, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to replace new neighbourhood planning support services with any other services.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827256, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of continuing to commission new neighbourhood planning support services.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827255, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changing the Planning Practice Guidance assessment criteria of identifying grey belt land from being judged as ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827254, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the consistency of Local Planning Authorities in identifying grey belt land.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827253, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the consistency of Local Planning Authorities in applying the (a) NPPF and (b) Planning Practice Guidance.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827252, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2025 to Question 58609 and the Answer of 26 March 2025 to Question 39471, for what reason only Green Belt purposes (a), (b) and (d) were include", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827251, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2025 to Question 58609 on Green Belt: Planning, and the Answer of 26 March 2025 to Question 39471 on Green Belt, for what reason her Department ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827241, "askingMemberId": 4441, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce cases of antisemitism.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827236, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70483", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the public sector trade union facility time data for the 2024-25 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827235, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70482", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 July 2025 to Question 69066 on Lobbying, whether he plans to (a) change the consultant lobbying regime and (b) undertake post-legislative scrutiny of the lobbying measures in the Tra", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827234, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70481", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on (a) advertising and (b) other services for the recruitment of the Director of the Government Communications Service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827233, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70480", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been spent on (a) signage, (b) furniture, (c) artwork and (d) stationery for the Deputy Prime Minister\u2019s office in his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827232, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70479", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which public body is responsible for investigating corruption in government procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827231, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70478", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether (a) his Department and (b) the Government Communications Service uses third-party providers to (i) assess, (ii) index and (iii) identify disinformation.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827230, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70477", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2025 to Question 65885 on Cabinet Office: Marketing, which digital and social media channels were used for paid advertising; whether this included digital influencers; and what ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827229, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70476", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the UK Multi-Stakeholder Forum for Open Government has met in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827228, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70475", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what data the Office for National Statistics holds on the average income of people by (a) class and (b) type of profession.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827227, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70474", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the headcount of staff included within the Government Communications Service is.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827226, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70473", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many suppliers were invited to bid for contract CCZZ24A18 under the Dynamic Purchasing System; how many bids were submitted; and for what reason the University of Birmingham was selected.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827225, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish any (a) external and (b) internal guidance produced for NATO members on what types of spending may be included in the definition of spending for (i) defence and (ii) security and resilience.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827224, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who will (a) procure and (b) own the nuclear weapons to be deployed on the F35-A fighter jets; and whether permission will be required from (i) NATO and (ii) the USA to (A) deploy and (B) launch them.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827139, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to allow motorcycles to access bus lanes by default.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827091, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70469", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff are (a) permanently assigned and (b) loaned to the New Media Unit; and what is the target for the total number of staff once it is fully recruited.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827090, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70468", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2024 to Question 16512 on Government Communication Service, and with reference to the FOI Internal Review response IR2025/05101 of 29 May 2025, if she will place in the Libra", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827089, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70467", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the FOI Internal Review response IR2025/05101 of 29 May 2025, if he will make it his policy to reduce the size of the Government Communication Service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827088, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70466", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department provides an annual allowance for works on the Chancellor\u2019s flat in Downing Street.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827087, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70465", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average annual value of London weighting for civil servants in his Department was in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827086, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70464", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his planned timetable is for the next audit of the Government Communication Service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827080, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70463", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2025 to Question 41438 on Government Departments: Conditions of Employment, whether his Department has issued guidance on the use of (a) zero hour contracts and (b) contingent la", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827079, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70462", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether appointments to the National Energy Systems Operator will be included in the Public Bodies Order in Council; whether the Chair appointment will be classified as a Significant Appointment.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827078, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70461", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what is the estimated average salary of a civil servant in the Government Communications Service, in the most recent period for which data is available; and what is the estimated monetary value of the employer c", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827077, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70460", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants in the (a) Cabinet Office and (b) Civil Service claim a London weighting on their salary, in the most recent period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827076, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70459", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what is the estimated (a) mean and (b) median salary of a civil servant in (i) 2024-25 and (ii) 2025-26, and what is the estimated monetary value of the employer contribution to their Civil Service pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827075, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70458", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2025 to Question 54270 on Government Departments: Directors, and with reference to the guidance entitled Non-Executive Board Member declaration of interests process, published on", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827074, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70457", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there is a target headcount for the size of the Civil Service.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827073, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70456", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Civil Service EDI Expenditure Review Data published on 29 May 2025, if he will list each of the external organisations that provided learning and development in 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827072, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70455", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2025 to Question 37432 on Prime Minister: Communication, and with reference to the Cabinet Office FOI Internal Review response IR2025/05101 of 29 May 2025, for what reason the ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827044, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70454", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference his Department's document entitled Conflict Resolution Department (CRD) Conflict Resolution Programme, Annual review (D0006064) 400035, published in October 20", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827043, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much his Department has paid to Inter Mediate since July 2024; and what (a) programmes and (b) purposes this funding was for.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827042, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70452", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2025 to Question 63325 on Armed Forces Day: Flags, whether 10 Downing Street flew the Armed Forces Day flag on Armed Forces Day in June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827041, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70451", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2025 to Question 57229 on Lord Mandelson, whether Lord Mandelson is permitted to (a) speak publicly at Labour Party fundraising events and (", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827049, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70450", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will consider the potential merits of reintroducing health in pregnancy grants to support early years development.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827177, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will extend the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme beyond this year.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827156, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 63307 on Ministry of Defence: Belfast, if he will provide a timeline for a decision being made on his Department's site at Dunmore.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827155, "askingMemberId": 4360, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will publish a breakdown of costs per government Department for the (a) Coagh and (b) Clonoe inquests.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827180, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answers of 13 June 2025 to Questions (a) 57249, (b) 57250 and (c) 57251, how many departmental roles are based in Aberdeen; what additional roles are planned for the city foll", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827160, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70445", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will respond to the report of the European Parliamentary Forum for Sexual & Reproductive Rights entitled The Next Wave: How Religious Extremism Is Regaining Power, published on 27 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827237, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of benefit rules on the risk of supported housing residents who increase their working hours being in rent arrears.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827204, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of how many and what proportion of people waited less than 6 weeks for their first treatment for talking therapies in (a) Newcastle upon Tyne and (b) North Tyneside in M", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827067, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the 10 Year Health Plan on victims of (a) modern slavery and (b) human trafficking.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827066, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the 10 Year Health Plan on people experiencing multiple forms of (a) social and (b) economic exclusion.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827199, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of funding reductions to the BBC World Service on the UK's ability to counter foreign threats.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827198, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the BBC World Service on the UK's soft power.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827197, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of allocating BBC World Service funding on a three year basis.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827196, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to develop a sustainable funding solution for the BBC World Service.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827201, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of enforcement powers available to local authorities in respect of developers who fail to comply with planning conditions ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827200, "askingMemberId": 4095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if her Department will issue guidance on the steps steps a local authority can take to compel a developer to comply with the conditions of their original planning consent relatin", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827189, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will consider reviewing the Allied Healthcare Professional status list to include chiropractors as part of the government\u2019s wider review of the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827188, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will (a) support further integration of chiropractic care into NHS services across Tatton and (b) give chiropractors Allied Healthcare Professional status.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827171, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department maintains a risk register of the UK-Mauritius Treaty over the future sovereignty of the Chagos Archipelago; and what assessment he has made of the pote", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827170, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to Article 5 of the treaty entitled UK/Mauritius: Agreement concerning the Chagos Archipelago including Diego Garcia (CS Mauritius No.1/2025), when he last dis", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827169, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to his Department's consultation document entitled Scheme design for bill discounts for transmission network infrastructure published on 8 August 2025, on what date will commun", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827168, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, If she will publish the details of the construction phase funding for the A12 Chelmsford to A120 Widening scheme considered by her Department\u2019s Investment Portfolio and Delivery Committee in 2023/24 and 2024/25", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827167, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, Pursuant to her Department\u2019s Annual Account 2024/25, with reference to page 19, (a) what funding she will be providing to each Mayoral Combined Authority in each financial year through to 2029/30, (b) what fund", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827166, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2025 to Question 67867 on East Anglia Rail Franchise: Nationalisation, which stakeholders she has (a) consulted and (b) engaged with in relation to the planned Services Agreeme", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827165, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, If she has undertaken an assessment of the net present value using the Green Book methodology of (a) the A12 Widening Scheme, (b) each of the infrastructure schemes referenced in her Oral Statement of 8 July 20", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827085, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2025 to Question 66153 on Housing: Construction, if she will publish the analysis of the A12 widening scheme conducted in accordance with the HMT Treasury Green Book and her De", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827084, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2025 to Question 66155 on A12: Repairs and Maintenance, how much funding she has allocated for the costs of ending the A12 widening scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827083, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2025 to Question 66157 on A12: Repairs and Maintenance, what resources she has made available for small-scale interventions on the A12.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827082, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2025 to Question 66154 on A12: Repairs and Maintenance, if she will publish the evidence she assessed when making the decision to cancel the A12 widening scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827081, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2025 to Question 67866 on A12: Repairs and Maintenance, when she plans to announce her Department's spending plans for the 2026-27 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827140, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS employees with a declared terminal diagnosis die when in (a) employment and (b) retirement.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827062, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2025 to Question 68387 on Epilepsy and Pregnancy: Sodium Valproate, what his Departments planned timeline is for establishing a centralised register caputring Preg", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827061, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2025 to Question 68387 on Epilepsy and Pregnancy: Sodium Valproate, whether his Department is taking steps to guarantee that every female valproate patient aged 13", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827060, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2025 to Question 68387 on Epilepsy and Pregnancy: Sodium Valproate, whether his Department plans to (a) mandate central tracking and annual reporting on how many w", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827059, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2025 to Question 68387 on Epilepsy and Pregnancy: Sodium Valproate, what steps his Department is taking to ensure (a) consistent and (b) effective implementation o", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827121, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of driving tests within (a) half an hour, (b) an hour and (c) two hours travel of the Gosport peninsula.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827120, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the role of swimming pools in delivering (a) health, (b) wellbeing and (c) community cohesion outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827119, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to work with (a) Swim England and (b) other stakeholders to prioritise swimming pool provision as part of the \u00a3400 million grassroots sport investment.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827118, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that the \u00a3400 million grassroots sport funding supports swimming pools in areas with limited access to aquatic facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827117, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the \u00a3400 million funding for grassroots sport facilities includes funding for energy efficiency upgrades in swimming pools.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827116, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the \u00a3400 million funding for grassroots sport facilities she plans to allocate to support the (a) development, (b) refurbishment and (c) sustainability of public swimming pools", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827115, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department plans to provide guidance to Ofcom on maintaining access to (a) affordable and (b) time-sensitive subscription publications, following changes to the Universal Service Obligation", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827114, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, in what way he is supporting small businesses to remain compliant with (a) VAT and (b) customs paperwork.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827113, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his Department\u2019s policies of the correspondence of 6 July 2025 from The Restart Project\u2019s on (a) product design codes, (b)", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827112, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of AI on (a) graduate employment, (b) employment in labour intensive industries, (c) employment in capital intensive industries and (d) overall emplo", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827111, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70405", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, will she make it her policy to commission the OBR to produce an AI impact assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827110, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70404", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions she has had with international partners on the potential impact of artificial intelligence on the fiscal outlook.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827109, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70403", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the (a) development and (b) dissemination of artificial intelligence on the tax base.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827108, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70402", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to pages 134-5 of the OBR\u2019s report entitled Fiscal risks and sustainability, published on 8 July 2025, what discussions she has had with the OBR on for what reason it categorised the rapid development", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827107, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70401", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she assumes increased productivity from AI adoption in her economic modelling.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827106, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70400", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the OBR\u2019s report entitled Fiscal risks and sustainability, published on 8 July 2025, what plans she has to commission the OBR to assess the fiscal implications of artificial intelligence.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827105, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70399", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of artificial intelligence on public expenditure.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827104, "askingMemberId": 4008, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70398", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of artificial intelligence on the fiscal outlook.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827203, "askingMemberId": 3997, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70397", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the cost of (a) quarterly tax returns and (b) mandatory use of Making Tax Digital for Income Tax software to small and medium enterprises.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827154, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Answer of 16 July 2025 to Question 66144 on Mental Health: Children and Young People, in designing future waves of the Mental Health: Children and Young People statistics coll", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827153, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what are the key differences between the National Security Online Information Team and its predecessor, the Counter-Disinformation Unit.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827152, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what is the proposed timetable for the Post Implementation Review of the Online Safety Act.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827103, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the average waiting times were for discharge pathways (a) 0, (b) 1, (c) 2 and (d) 3 in (i) England, (ii) Hampshire and the Isle of Wight ICB area and (iii) ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827102, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in each Integrated Care Board area, (a) what the resident population is and (b) how many full-time equivalent clinical staff are employed in (i) community hospital in-patient care and (ii) home-bas", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827101, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the ratio of community hospital beds to acute hospital beds is in (a) England (b) Hampshire and the Isle of Wight and (c) the Portsmouth Hospitals University NHS Trust area.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827100, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department issues guidance on a target ratio of step-down beds to acute beds in an acute hospital\u2019s catchment area.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827222, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2025 to Question 31833 on Mineworkers' Pension Scheme, when he expects discussions with Mineworkers' Pension Scheme trustees to conclude on the future of the", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827162, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will add priority species-rich grasslands to the list of irreplaceable habitats.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827161, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will review the definition of irreplaceable habitats to ensure it is (a) robust and (b) comprehensive to support decision makers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827159, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that independent celebrants are included in the Government response to the Law Commission\u2019s report entitled Celebrating Marriage: A New Weddings Law, published on 18 July 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827158, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the decision to pause the next phase of electrification of the Midland Main Line on rail (a) times and (b) investment in the East Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827157, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has he made of the potential merits of increasing parental bereavement leave from two weeks to four weeks.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827048, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with poultry industry representatives on the potential welfare merits of upright catching.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827047, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her Department's policy is on converting existing tennis courts to padel courts.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827238, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department plans to take to amend the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 to include decapod crustaceans.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827211, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2025 to Question 51054 on Teachers: Workplace Pensions, what progress has been made on reducing the number of teachers waiting for compensation since 30 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827207, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how she defines mainly by retail in Clause 15 of the Crime and Policing Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827202, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she intends the offence of assaulting a shop worker to apply to people working in a bureau de change.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827179, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Welfare of Animals (Transport) (Amendment) Regulations 2025 on the (a) stress and (b) injury chances of farmed chickens and t", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827132, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that all British Overseas Territories have implemented publicly accessible registers for beneficial ownership before the end of the year.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827131, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of extending Northern Ireland\u2019s rules for new drivers to all new drivers across the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827069, "askingMemberId": 3924, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of creating a fashion watchdog to help tackle exploitation in the supply chains of clothing manufacturers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827068, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to include motorcycling in its planned Integrated National Transport Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827052, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has considered the potential impact of the recent consultation on Biodiversity Net Gain on (a) investors and (b) developers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827051, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason his Department is consulting on proposals to change Biodiversity Net Gain requirements for small sites and medium sites one year after Biodiversity Net Gain became mand", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827050, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of changes to Biodiversity Net Gain requirements for small and medium sites on nature.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827046, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support (a) refugees and (b) displaced Ukrainians with leave to remain in the UK to (i) secure decent employment and (ii) improve their English language skills.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827182, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will have discussions with Historic Royal Palaces on improving the (a) visibility and (b) marketing of categories of discounted tickets.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827181, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will have discussions with Historic Royal Palaces on discounted tickets for UK nationals.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827174, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-10T00:00:00", "uin": "70366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence plans to publish updated guidance on the eight types of hernia mesh.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827145, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "70365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 August 2025 to Question 65738 on Foetal Valproate Spectrum Disorder, if he will make interim payments to valproate families following the end of the pilot project.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827137, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "70364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the outcome was of the MHRA rectopexy review.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827136, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "70363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if there is a Hospital Episode Statistics code used to record instances of mesh used for rectopexy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827058, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has held discussions with (a) retailers and (b) producers on the pricing of alcohol-free drinks.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827057, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has made an assessment of for what reason alcohol-free drinks are priced (a) comparably to and (b) higher than alcoholic equivalents.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827056, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70360", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has considered the potential merits of (a) tax and (b) subsidy incentives in reducing the cost of alcohol-free drinks.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827055, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70359", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of (a) VAT rates and (b) other fiscal measures on the relative pricing of (i) alcohol-free and (ii) alcoholic drinks.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827054, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has had discussions with industry stakeholders on the pricing strategies of (a) alcohol-free drinks and (b) alcoholic beverages.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827053, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will hold discussions with (a) manufacturers and (b) retailers on improving the affordability of alcohol-free alternatives.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827206, "askingMemberId": 1482, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Typhoon Force in providing security until the Tempest programme becomes operational.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827221, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support young Ukrainians commencing their (a) primary, (b) secondary and (c) tertiary education in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827220, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect freedom of religion (a) Albania, (b) Serbia, (c) Bosnia and (d) other European countries.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827219, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his counterpart in Iran on the safe return of dual British nationals imprisoned in Iran.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827218, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Israel, (b) Lebanon, (c) Jordan and (d) Egypt on access to education for children fleeing Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827217, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to support access to education for children fleeing Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827216, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote religious freedom in Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827215, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to support lower-income countries in tackling health risks posed by inadequate public housing.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827214, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that local radio stations continue to meet their commitments to locally produced content under the Media Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827213, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether Ofcom has reviewed the compliance of Nation Broadcasting with the original licence conditions of Time 107.5 FM following its (a) rebranding and (b) programming changes.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827212, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the sale of Time 107.5 FM to Nation Broadcasting on the provision of (a) local news and (b) community programming in Romford constituency", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827187, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the transparency data entitled Building Safety Regulator building control approval application data October 2023 to March 2025, published on 9 July 2025, when s", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827186, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the transparency data entitled Building Safety Regulator building control approval application data October 2023 to March 2025, published on 9 July 2025, whethe", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827185, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish (a) training and (b) reference material given to Building Safety Regulator (i) Case Officers, (ii) Regulatory Leads, (iii) Principal Regulatory Leads and (iv)", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827184, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what training is given to Building Safety Regulator (a) Case Officers, (b) Regulatory Leads, (c) Principal Regulatory Leads and (d) external Multi-disciplinary Team members on (i", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827151, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that local radio stations continue to meet their commitments to locally produced content under the Media Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827150, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether Ofcom has reviewed the compliance of Nation Broadcasting with the original licence conditions of Time 107.5 FM, following its (a) rebranding and (b) programming changes.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827149, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the sale of Time 107.5 FM to Nation Broadcasting on the provision of (a) local news and (b) community programming in Romford con", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827065, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make it her department's policy to ban (a) bilingual and (b) and foreign language street signs.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827064, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to deport immigrants found guilty of violent crimes.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827045, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the safety of (a) over the counter and (b) prescription grade sun cream in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827142, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the Royal Air Force\u2019s E-7 Wedgetail airborne early warning aircraft flypast at the Royal International Air Tattoo at RAF Fairford in July 2025 was cancelled.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827129, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2025 to Question 68356 on Air Force: Boeing E-7, whether any component of the UK E-7 Wedgetail sustainment contract will involve (a) logistical, (b) maintenance and (c) technical", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827128, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any structural modifications carried out on WT001 post-delivery revealed unforeseen integration challenges with (a) the MESA radar and (b) other mission systems.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827127, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2025 to Question 67826 on Boeing E-7: Standards, what enforcement measures are available for his Department to use if the incentivisation milestones are missed; and whether any o", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827126, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2025 to Question 65212 on Northern Ireland Troubles (Legacy and Reconciliation) Act 2023, whether his Department plans to lay the draft Northern Ireland Troubles (Legacy", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827123, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to Question 62175 on Ajax Vehicles: Journalism, tabled by the hon. Member for Rayleigh and Wickford on 24 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827122, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information his Department holds on the number of people who had previously received an on-the-run letter that have since been (a) charged with and (b) prosecuted for terrorist offences.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827240, "askingMemberId": 1440, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, where the embedded hubs for the Immigration Prison Teams are located; which prisons are included in each hub; and how many Immigration Officers are employed in each hub.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827239, "askingMemberId": 1440, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Immigration Officers are were employed in the operational arm of the Foreign National Offender Returns Command Immigration Prison Team on 29 August 2025; which prisons those officers are base", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827148, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make representations to the UN on the need for an independent verifiable assessment of the number of missiles fired by Hamas into Israel between (a) July 2022 and ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827144, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2025 to Question 53819 on Ministry of Justice: Translation Services, what was the change in the cost of language services between 2019 and 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827143, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70324", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the change in the estimated worth of the frozen assets of the previous Libyan regime between 2011 and 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827138, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he plans to take to help encourage private sector investment in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827210, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with representatives of the hospitality industry on job losses in the West Midlands since the Autumn Budget 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827209, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 July 2025 to Question 69007 on Stop and Search: West Midlands, whether the number of times stop and search powers were used under Serious Violence Reduction Orders in the ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827147, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what metrics are used to assess the (a) uptake and (b) effectiveness of the Ask for Angela scheme; and what information her Department holds on its usage in licensed venues.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827146, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70319", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking with financial institutions to provide (a) (i) emergency and (ii) discreet access to banking, (b) financial independence tools, (c) specialist support services and (d) other (A) privacy and ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827130, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the rate of people who were killed or seriously injured between junctions 31 and 33 of the M6 in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827099, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase climate resilience in agriculture.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827098, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to increase (a) cycling safety and (b) increase uptake of cycling in (i) Preston and (ii) Lancashire.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827097, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure the safety of asylum seekers accommodated in hotels in the North West, in the context of rising community tensions.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827096, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to prevent arson attacks on hotels housing asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827095, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with domestic abuse allegations have gone on to be convicted for offences related to public disorder or extremism in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827094, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of domestic violence had a known mental health disorder in (a) Preston and (b) Lancashire in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827195, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the National Cancer Plan will include targets to improve timely diagnosis of (a) myeloma and (b) other blood cancers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827194, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS staff who are assaulted at work do not face (a) loss of pay, (b) punitive attendance management processes and (c) risk of dismissal while reco", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827193, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that companies comply with section 830 of the Companies Act 2006 on dividend payments; and whether he plans to (a) strengthen enforcement and (b) introduce", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827192, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2025 to Question 61726, if he will publish: (a) the data source for the reported 8.9% increase in doctors working in clinical oncology between 2021 and 2023, (b) t", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827191, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will amend Section 100 of the Criminal Justice Act 2003 to prevent irrelevant previous disclosures being used as bad character evidence in sexual offence trials; and if she will issue guidance to the (a) C", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827190, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the (a) ethical, (b) legal, and (c) safeguarding implications of UK residents entering commercial surrogacy arrangements overseas; and whether the G", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827135, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for UK counter-terrorism cooperation of the detention of Bechir Akremi; and whether he has considered the findings o", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827134, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Tunisian counterpart on (a) the detention of political figures in Tunisia in recent years and (b) compliance with the International Coven", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827133, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Tunisian counterpart on (a) the mass trial of political figures in April 2025 and (b) the need for (i) due process and (ii) hum", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827125, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to revise the document entitled The Principles governing intelligence sharing to include an explicit prohibition on authorising cooperation where there is a real risk of t", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827124, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department's review of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance guidance will include consideration of specific cases in which assistance was provided despite", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827071, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to reform specialist provision for children with SEND.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827070, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to include dementia specialist nurses in the Neighbourhood Health Service model; and what steps he is taking to ensure access to dementia specialist nurses in every co", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827063, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the report by Bite Back entitled Fuel us, don't fool us, published in July 2025; and what steps she is taking to strengthen compliance with t", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827183, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "70297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will withdraw outstanding Technical Capability Notices relating to encryption.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827141, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "70296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information his Department holds on the number of suspected IRA members accused of terrorism offences between 1970 and 1990 that were later acquitted.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827178, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, on what dates the Chagos Contact Group (a) has met and (b) has plans to meet.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827176, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many full-time equivalent civil servants are working on policy related to nuclear test veterans.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827175, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the disability employment gap in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827173, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the UK-US Economic Prosperity Deal on the agricultural sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827164, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if his Department has conducted an analysis of how many websites showing pornographic content have complied with the age verification requirement as set out in the Online Safety Act 202", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827163, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Money and Pensions Service has spent on equipment to enable staff to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827093, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70289", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much National Savings and Investments has spent on equipment to enable staff to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827092, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve\u00a0infant feeding\u00a0support in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827208, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle age discrimination in the workplace.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827223, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to proposed local government reorganisation in Hampshire and the Isle of Wight, what protection will be given to the (a) culture and (b) interests of the New Fores", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827205, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she plans to take to increase protection of town and parish council clerks against bullying by elected councillors.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827172, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate his Department has made of the numbers of Afghan (a) interpreters and (b) other personnel, who assisted UK armed forces and remain at risk from the Taliban whilst stranded in (i) Afghanistan ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827038, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "70283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of women to have died since the publication of the Government\u2019s Response to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman\u2019s Investigation into and Re", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827040, "askingMemberId": 39, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of cancer patients receive treatment within 62 days in (a) England and (b) Maldon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827039, "askingMemberId": 39, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to publicise the need for vaccination against (a) influenza and (b) covid-19.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827033, "askingMemberId": 1440, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visits by Immigration Officers have taken place in each Scottish prison in each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827032, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "70279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to pages 12 and 19 of the report published by the Office for Students entitled Financial sustainability of higher education providers in England: 2025, published on 8 May 2025, what steps her Dep", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827030, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-28T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "905469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential impact of the time taken to respond to the Hughes Report recommendations on women impacted by valproate and pelvic mesh.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1827029, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-08-28T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "905439", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for his policies of representations received by his Department on its proposed reforms to inheritance tax on farms.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1827029", "method": "GET"}]}]